Reiner!
Eren!
I think the fight's over. We're out of strength.
At this point, I can't exactly kill Reiner.
In that case, let's go back home.
See you later, Reiner.
Protect the airship from below!
Use every last shot you've got!
They're retreating... Does this mean we're safe?
They're running.
Gabi!
Eren Jaeger!
You won't get away! I'm gonna kill you!
"Assassin's Bullet"
Damn, you're a filthy sight.
You fall in a pile of shit?
Eren...
Captain...
This brings back memories, Eren.
You have such a kickable face.
After you're all tied up, we'll have a chat.
That's fine, but I explained
everything in the letters.
Did you not understand it?
That face... It reminds me of the
rotten shits who lived underground.
Never thought I'd see it on you.
Cheer up. Everything happened like you wanted.
Stop 'em! Kill every last one you can!
Everybody, in! They've got nothing
to take down an airship!
Jean!
You go! I'll hold the rear!
It's all you, Commander Lobov!
I told you, I'm a recruit!
Nobody needs the Garrison anymore!
Especially not some overpaid geezer!
Jean!
Grab on!
Who's left?
Still waiting on Lima Squad.
As far as we know, there're six casualties.
I see... Shit!
That's nothing compared to the damage we did!
It's a huge victory!
The New Eldian Empire's
first battle ends in victory!
--Yeah!
Tonight, we celebrate in honor
of our six fallen heroes!
First battle, huh?
How many more till the fighting ends?
Just how many have to die?
Anyways, I'm just glad we survived again.
It's not very fair to the others,
but you guys are special...
...to me.
That hurts, idiot. Don't hug us
wearing hard-ass gear.
Excuse me, Jean?! You're the idiot for
always fussing over your tiny-ass beard!
Huh?
That's right! Why grow a beard
if you can't eat it?
Huh?!
Say, are we eating soon?
Not till we reach the island.
What a useless leader you are.
Gabi!
Gabi, wait!
C'mon, that's enough.
They're flying away.
Running after them is pointless.
Even you know that.
Zofia...
Zofia's body was crushed under debris.
I was sitting right next to her.
Udo tried to help her,
but he got trampled by the stampede.
Stepped on, over and over,
until his head split open.
And the two gate guards... They stopped me.
I was trying to run back to the plaza.
I'm an Eldian, but they told me to
turn back because it's dangerous.
Then they were shot by a girl
on the roof and died.
Being an Eldian born in the zone,
people spit at me when I go outside.
I've had a lot of miserable memories,
but that's why I try so hard.
To show the world that Eldians
are good people!
So that someday, we could be proud
of our Eldian armbands!
I worked hard believing it could happen!
But they crushed everything!
This internment zone is my home!
It's where the people I care about live!
Isn't trampling on it unforgivable?!
And yet, you're telling me
not to run after them?
When Zeke was killed before our eyes
and we could do nothing?
Not knowing why any of this happened?!
Why, Reiner? Why was my mom eaten by a Titan?
They were trampled on.
Huh?
The enemy was attacked by Marley
Warriors and lots of people died.
This is revenge.
Did you... see it happen?
No, I didn't.
Neither did I.
Besides, they're all just island devils
who threaten world peace.
You should know that! They're cruel
devils who've always deserved to die.
They're nothing like us.
Reiner, I'm the same as you.
Across the sea, within the walls...
It's the same.
Lima Squad? That means everyone's aboard.
Tell the bridge we're good to ascend!
Roger!
Huh?
A kid?!
It hit!
It's still attached...
Gabi!
What do you think you're doing?!
This trigger... If I pull it...
Gabi... Don't tell me you're
thinking of boarding it!
I'm gonna kill those island devils!
You'll just end up dead, idiot!
Tell my mom and dad.
Let Reiner and the others know:
That I fought till the end.
Even if we don't win today,
you guys will carry on my will.
Falco! Gabi!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
My brother...
Goodbye, Falco.
You were one of the good ones.
You have to rescue Gabi
from the dark future that awaits us.
Falco!
Falco?!
Why?!
The one who should inherit
the Armored Titan... is me!
Huh?!
Did you hear a sound just now?
Hey! Quiet down!
Make some noise! Victory!
--Yeah!
Hey!
Isn't Lobov still out there?
No, I think he came aboard.
Sasha!
"The military's official bolt-action rifle fires
five shots and can be equipped with the
standard-issue knife as a bayonet. They are used
by Marley's Warrior unit, army, and navy."
You bastard!
Sasha! Hey!
Hang in there! Hey!
You're so... damn loud...
Are we... eating soon?
Bandages, now!
We've gotta stop the bleeding!
Right!
Sasha! Make it to the island!
Meat...
Jean, they climbed aboard
using Lobov's ODM gear.
I'll toss 'em outside. All right?
If we toss kids out of an airship,
will the killing ever end?
What happened to Braun and Grice?
They ran off without warning
and never came back.
Pieck...
Commander, I remember...
There was a Marley soldier who
led Galliard and me into a trap.
I remember seeing that
same soldier three years ago.
They were on the first scout fleet sent
to Paradis after Reiner came back.
The missing scout ships?
Yes. I'm sure of it.
They looked so awful with a beard.
Hey, you gonna wear that forever?
Huh? I thought it was well-received.
They're still celebrating?
Don't touch me, you devils!
We haven't lost yet!
The rest of our comrades will carry
on the will of War Chief Zeke!
Gabi, stop!
What do we do with 'em, Jean?
Us true Eldians are gonna
haunt you till you die!
Pass that on to your
ringleader after I'm dead!
I'll take you to him.
You can tell him exactly what you told me.
How'd you identify the soldier?
Well, it's someone I had
a particular interest in.
Because... she's a devout follower of Zeke.
Gabi... Falco...? Why are you here?
Why? Why are you?
You're alive?! Why did you
let them capture you?!
Who are these kids?
They killed Lobov and used
his gear to come aboard.
Sasha was shot by this one here.
I don't think she's gonna make it.
It's all you, Onyankopon.
You got it, Hange!
Well? Did everything play out
as you hoped, Zeke Jaeger?
Huh?
For the most part,
but there were a few miscalculations.
Zeke...?
Huh? Who are these kids?
Miscalculations.
Yelena! What the hell happened
to trapping the Cart and Jaw?!
People died because of you!
I'm sorry. I assure you they fell
down the hole, but it's still my fault.
And to cover for that slip-up, the Beast
chucked more rocks at us than planned.
That was some clever improv for a clown
like you. Wouldn't you say, hairball?
Don't glare at me like that, Levi.
What if I piss my pants?
And you're quite the actor yourself,
considering you want to kill me so bad.
I'm the kind of person
who saves the best bite for last.
I like to savor the taste.
We killed the Marley brass
and destroyed their port and fleet.
That should buy us some time.
Until the whole world launches
a joint attack on Paradis?
Every time you're caught by the enemy,
we sacrifice lives to get you back.
No matter how many it takes.
And yet knowing that, you went
so far as to make yourself a hostage.
Just like you hoped,
we didn't have much choice.
You put your trust in us
and we lost our trust in you.
But now we have the Founding Titan
and a Titan with royal blood.
The cost of those sacrifices
will be paid through Eldia's freedom.
Sasha...
...is dead.
Conny.
Did Sasha... have any last words?
She said... "Meat."
I brought some meat from
the officers' storehouse!
It'll be fine!
We can just raise more cattle and sheep
once we retake our land!
Eren... Sasha only died because you
dragged the Scouts into this.
Could they have taken some other path?
Unable to change the past, they must
continue down the one before them.
Next episode: "Brave Volunteers."